SERGEY RADKOV

Boise ID USA | (208) 371-3904 | radkovsn@gmail.com | www.sradkov.com

www.linkedin.com/in/radkovsn

https://github.com/eriixon

Permanent Work Authorization No Visa Sponsorship Required

TECHNOLOGIES

Languages

C#

JavaScriprt TypeScript HTML CSS

Java Python

Frameworks

.NET ASP.NET
Vue JS React
Angular JS Angular
Boostrap 3 &4 Semantic UI

Storage

Microsoft SQL Firebase none SQL

Tools

Node JS Express JS
Yarn NPM
Redux jQuery
GitHub Heroku
NumPy SciPy
Magento Pega

RESTful Web services Microsoft Visual Studio Microsoft Visual Studio Code IDEA PyCharm IDEA WebStorm

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Practical problem solver with exceptional attention to detail
- Strong presentation, communication and negotiation skills
- Demonstrated success in project and staff management
- Ability to adapt to rapidly changing environments

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A web and software developer with 2+ years of experience and a reputation for being a creative and self-motivated problem-solver, a team player adjusting well to people and environment, with positive attitude, a quick learner who is committed to continuous learning and enjoys challenges, and a hard worker always willing to jump in and help out when needed. As a software developer I have a keen interest in technology, web and mobile applications and user experience.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

System Architect | Ruletek | Meridian, Idaho | 04.2018 – now

Worked as part of a team to design, build, and support BPM applications for clients, developed system features and functionality out of user requirements, designed and develop user interfaces, followed design methodologies, completing applications using languages and software products.

Technologies: Pega 7.*, Robotics, C#, HTML, CSS, SQL

Back-End Web Developer | Neoreef | Boise, Idaho | 09.2017 – 02.2018

Developed reusable code and libraries for future use for the unique proprietary content management system, integration of user-facing elements developed by a front-end developers with server side logic.

Technologies: .NET, ASP.NET, C#, VB, SQL, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS

Web Developer | Saharacase LLC | Boise, Idaho | 11.2016 - 09.2017

Developed a vibrant, secure website using interactive features and SEO best practices to optimize traffic, page views and the user experience (UX), develop product web templates for major online marketplaces.

Technologies: JavaScript, JQuery, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootsrap 3, Magento 1/2

Web Developer | freelance | Boise, Idaho | 06.2016 – 11.2016

Created and maintained web pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, AngularJS and Node.js, optimized web pages for mobile.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AngularJS, Bootsrap 3

Senior Product Engineer | Volvo Truck Russia | Moscow, Russia | 2010 -2015 Promoted Volvo telematics services, established new consulting services

EDUCATION

Back End with .NET C# Course

BoiseCodeWorks | Boise, Idaho | 2017

Web Development Immersive Full Stack Course

BoiseCodeWorks | Boise, Idaho | 2016

The leading premier coding bootcamp in Idaho.

Java Level 1, 2, 3 On-line Course

GeekBrains | Moscow, Russia | 2015

The leading online coding school in Russia.

Master's Degree | Transport Engineering Economics and Management

State University of Management | Moscow, Russia | 1997 – 2002

Russia's leading university in the field of management education.